(Sheldon:)Leonard, you are my roommate,
my source of transportation...
(Sheldon:)...and you help me fold my sheets
when they come out of the dryer.
(Sheldon:)You are safe.
- Can I whistle?
- Don't be silly.
(Penny:)Howard...
(Sheldon:)...you do not have a Ph.D.
(Sheldon:)Your cologne is an assault on the senses.
(Sheldon:)And you're not available for video games
during the Jewish High Holidays.
- Guilty as charged. I'm out.
- No.
(Sheldon:)You, too, are safe.
(Howard:)Come on. What do I have to do?
(Penny:)Okay, you know what?
I see where this is going.
(Penny:)I'm not one of you guys.
(Penny:)- I'm not a scientist, so...
Penny...
(Sheldon:)...everything you're saying is true,
but please allow me to continue.
(Sheldon:)Raj, you're out.
It's a good question.
(Sheldon:)While you do provide
a certain cultural diversity...
...to a homogenous group, your responses
to the questionnaire were truly disturbing.